phonerated.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy : Phonerated's Privacy Policy - Phonerated.com

This Privacy Policy was last modified on June 24th, 2016.

Phonerated's privacy policy is quite simple: 

  * We are not collecting any email or any kind of personal information.

  * If some of our applications ask for your cell phone number, we won't store them unless otherwise noted.

  * The only information we look at is the very common and anonymous user behavior data provided by Google Analytics.

  * We use anonymous cookies for certain features, like our ringtone matcher quiz, our celliminator phone chooser, and things like learning what links are most popular. Additionally, the ad agencies we do business with may use cookies, just like those of any other website that displays advertisements.

Our main motivation is simply to create the best web site to find the best cell phone and service plan for your needs and we don't need to know your birth date to accomplish that. 

Phonerated ("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.Phonerated.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of Phonerated.com.

We don't collect much personal information and we use it only for providing and improving Phonerated.com. By using Phonerated.com, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at http://www.Phonerated.com.

**Log Data**  
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. We use navigation statistics in a non-nominal way.

**Cookies**  
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Phonerated makes very little use of cookies, but some features, such as the comparison tool, may use them to store your personal preference or comparison list. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

**Security**  
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links To Other Sites**  
Our Site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

Phonerated has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party sites or services.

**Changes To This Privacy Policy**  
Phonerated may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on Phonerated.com. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.

**Affiliate pariticipation**  
Phonerated participates in various affiliate programs. Phonerated is a participant in the Amazon Inc. associates program of many countries, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com (or any other Amazon domain name pertinent to a given country, such as Amazon.co.uk, Amazon.ca, etc). Amazon and the Amazon logo are trademarks of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](http://www.phonerated.com/contact-us.php).

Don't Be Selfish & Let Others Know... Share This Page
